ANTIGRAVITY v5.1 - EXECUTIVE STRIKE PROTOCOL ACTIVE

--- STEP 1: Executive Handshake ---
Calling https://empire-unified-backup-production-6d15.up.railway.app/bridge/performance...
Status: 200
Handshake Success!
Funnel: Total Leads: 615, Active: 2, Positive: 1

--- STEP 2: Physical Email Strike (GHL Webhook) ---
Triggering GHL Webhook Strike to nearmiss1193@gmail.com...
GHL Webhook Triggered Successfully. Status: 200

--- STEP 3: Upgraded Grok Integration Test ---
Checking Available Grok Models...
Using Model: grok-2-vision-1212
Sending Upgraded Prompt to grok-2-vision-1212...
Grok Response: Hey Daniel! Here are three simple leads for Lakeland businesses that could use an ROI rescue:

1. **Lakeland's Local Bakery** - Imagine a cozy bakery in downtown Lakeland that's been struggling to make ends meet. They've got delicious treats but not enough customers. We can pitch them on how Sarah AI can help them find new customers by analyzing local trends and preferences, boosting their sales and saving their business!

2. **Lakeland Fitness Studio** - There's a small fitness studio that's seen better days. They're losing members because they can't compete with bigger gyms. We can tell them Sarah AI can analyze what fitness trends are hot in Lakeland, helping them tailor their classes to what people want, bringing back old members and attracting new ones, rescuing their ROI!

3. **Lakeland's Green Thumb Nursery** - This nursery has beautiful plants but isn't selling as much as they used to. They need help to grow their business. We can suggest Sarah AI to look into what plants are popular in Lakeland right now, and how to market them better online and locally, turning their green thumbs into green profits!

For each of these, we'll say something like, "Hi there! I'm Sarah AI, and I'm here to rescue your business's ROI. Let's work together to bring in more customers and make your business thrive again in Lakeland!" Simple, friendly, and to the point!
Grok Integration Verified.

≡ƒÅå MISSION SUCCESS: Execution Mode Operational. Ready for full prospecting.
